buxim.com 2017-12-06

# Privacy Policy | BuySellAds

## Purpose of the Privacy Policy

BuySellAds.com Inc. ("Company", "we" or "us") provides advertising technology solutions that enables media companies, online advertisers, and web publishers to buy, sell, and measure the effectiveness of their advertising campaigns. In order to accomplish this, we have created and manage online (as well as on a mobile basis) certain applications ("App" or "Apps") and related support and hosting services (the "Service" or "Services").

We are committed to respecting and protecting the privacy rights of our users, and we created this Privacy Policy to give you notice of how your private information will (and will not) be used by us. This Privacy Policy provides information on our policies and procedures regarding the collection, use and disclosure of personal information we receive from (1) Companies and individuals who use the Apps created by us and (2) visitors who simply browse the Web Site or Apps ("Visitors"). 

**By using or accessing the Service in any manner, you acknowledge that you accept the practices and policies outlined in this Privacy Policy, and you hereby consent that we will collect, use, and share your information in the following ways.**

Remember that your use of the Service is at all times subject to the Terms of Service, which incorporates this Privacy Policy. Any terms we use in this Policy without defining them have the definitions given to them in the Terms of Service.

This Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time. We will notify you of any material changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on the Site. You are advised to consult this policy regularly for any changes.

### 1\. What Information Do We Collect and How Do We Collect It?

At various times, you could be asked to provide information such as your name, email address, contact phone number or other information. Information collected is often defined as being either anonymous or personally identifiable:

Anonymous Information refers to information that cannot be tied back to a specific individual. For instance, we may know that thousands of people have visited this Privacy Policy, but we do not necessarily know their names, where they live, or their date of birth. What we collect from visits such as this constitutes anonymous information. Some of the individuals who access our Services decline to use the personalization features that are available to them, and therefore those individuals are anonymous to us and the only data we collect about them is anonymous information.

Personally Identifiable Information refers to information that tells us specifically who you are, such as your name, email address, or phone number. Using an App may allow the Company to "recognize" you to allow us to personalize our service for you.

#### Anonymous Information

As is true of most apps and web sites, we gather certain information (such as mobile provider, operating system, etc.) automatically and store it in log files. We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the app, to track users movements around the App and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may link some of this automatically-collected data to certain Personally Identifiable Information.

#### Personally Identifiable Information

When you register with us via our website or an App, we may ask you for some personally identifiable information, such as your first and last name, email address, home address, and other information. If you are an advertiser, we need you to provide certain billing information, such as credit card, bank account or PayPal information. If you are a publisher of ads, we need you to provide information about your website and payment method, such as bank or PayPal account information. You may review and update this personally identifiable information in your profile by logging in and editing such information in your dashboard. If you decide to delete all of your information, we may cancel your account. We may retain an archived copy of your records as required by law or for reasonable business purposes.

Some Personally Identifiable Information may also be provided to intermediaries and third parties who assist us with the Apps and the Service, but who may make no use of any such information other than to assist us in providing the Service. Except as otherwise provided in this Privacy Policy, however, we will not rent or sell your Personally Identifiable Information to third parties.

If you choose to allow an App to collect your location data, such location data will be available to us. In addition, if you have an account with Facebook, Twitter, Google+, LinkedIn, Foursquare or other similar websites (each a "Social Network"), your Social Network identity, including your public picture, may be associated with your location data. 

If you send a "Do Not Track" request through your web browser, we may still collect and use your browsing data to improve security, to provide our Service and to generate reporting statistics, but in general we will not track other web sites that you may have visited.

BuySellAds.com Inc. is the owner of the information collected through the Service.

#### No Information Collected from Children.

We will never knowingly collect any personal information from children under the age of 13. If we obtain actual knowledge that we have collected personal information from a child under the age of 13, that information will be immediately removed from any access. Because we do not collect such information, we have no such information to use or to disclose to third parties. We have designed this policy in order to comply with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act ("COPPA").

### 2\. How Do We Use Individual Information?

#### General Use

We use personal information mainly to provide the Services and may also contact users regarding account activities, new version and product offerings, or other communications relevant to the Services. We do not sell or share any personally identifiable or other information to any third parties.

If you contact us by email or by filling-out a registration form, we may keep a record of your contact information and correspondence, and may use your email address, and any information that you provide to us in your message, to respond to you. In addition, we may use the personal information described above to send you information regarding the Apps and/or the Services. If you decide at any time that you no longer wish to receive such information or communications from us, email us at [support@buysellads.com](mailto:support@buysellads.com) and request to be removed from our list. The circumstances under which we may share such information with third parties are described in part (4) below.

### 3\. How Do We Store Your Personal Information?

#### Storage of Individual Information

The Company operates or leases secure data networks protected by industry standard firewall and password protection systems. Our security and privacy policies are periodically reviewed and enhanced as necessary, and only authorized individuals have access to the information. Notwithstanding such measures, we cannot guarantee that our security measures will prevent our computers from being illegally accessed, and the individual information on them stolen or altered.

Your account is protected by a password for your privacy and security. You must prevent unauthorized access to your account and Personal Information by selecting and protecting your password appropriately and limiting access to your computer or device and browser by signing off after you have finished accessing your account.

#### Third Party Hosting, Serving and Storage

COMPANY MAY CONTRACT WITH A VARIETY OF THIRD PARTY SUPPLIERS/PROVIDERS/VENDORS/SOCIAL NETWORKS FROM TIME TO TIME, TO PROVIDE FOR OUR HOSTING, AUTHENTICATION, CREDIT CARD PAYMENT, SERVING, STORAGE AND TELECOMMUNICATION NEEDS, ETC., INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION STORAGE OF OUR USERS PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION. WE SHALL NOT BE RESPONSIBLE NOR LIABLE FOR, AND HEREBY DISCLAIMS, ALL RESPONSIBILITY AND LIABILITY FOR CULPABLE (INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION NEGLIGENT) ACTS OR OMISSIONS BY OUR THIRD PARTY SUPPLIERS/VENDORS.

### 4\. Do We Disseminate Any Personal Information?

#### Service Providers

We may use third parties to help operate and distribute our Apps, authenticate users and deliver products and services, and may share limited Personally Identifiable Information with our service providers, vendors, suppliers, and other third parties that provide products or services for or through this Service (such as Web Site or database hosting companies, authentication providers, address list hosting companies, e-mail service providers, analytics companies, distribution companies and other similar service providers that use such information on our behalf). Unless otherwise stated, these companies do not have any right to use the Personally Identifiable Information we provide to them beyond what is necessary for them to assist us.

#### Aggregate Statistics

We may disclose aggregate statistics regarding user behavior as a measure of interest in, and use of, our Service, our Apps and e-mails to third parties in the form of aggregate data, such as overall patterns or demographic reports that do not describe or identify any individual user or client.

#### Complying with Legal Process

We take reasonable steps to ensure the privacy of data uploaded. We reserve the right to use or disclose your Personally Identifiable Information and other information in response to subpoenas, court orders, warrants, or legal process, or to otherwise establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims or in the event you violate or breach an agreement with us. We may use and disclose your Personally Identifiable Information if we believe you will harm the property or rights of Company, its owners, or others. 

#### Business Transitions

In the event the Company goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets as well as in the event of a bankruptcy, assignment for benefit of creditors or receivership, your Personally Identifiable Information may be disclosed and will likely be among the assets transferred. You may be notified thereafter via prominent notice on our web site for 30 days of any such change in ownership or control of your personal information. We further reserve the right to disclose, transfer or sell your personal information to companies who are affiliated with us in our sole discretion.

### 5\. Do We Allow Foreign Use of the Apps?

To the extent that you are accessing our Apps in the United States while domiciled outside of the United States, you acknowledge that the Personally Identifiable Information you are providing us may be collected and stored in the United States and elsewhere and therefore consent to the transfer of information to and storage of the information outside of your domiciled country and in the United States.

### 6\. Information About the Technology

Apps may employ cookies to collect non-personally identifying information in the course of providing clients with ad-serving services and for the purpose of helping clients determine which advertisement is suitable to be delivered to a user. A cookie is a small text file that can be stored on a user's computer when that computer's browser views an advertisement or website of one of our clients. The cookie is associated with and unique to the specific computer. The cookie does not contain the user's name, address, phone number, email address, or anything that personally identifies it. We collect into the cookie only non-personally identifying information such as the type of the computer's operating system, type of internet browser software, what web pages were viewed and at what time, and geographic location of user's internet service provider.

#### Removing Our 3rd Party Ad-Serving Cookie from Your Browser

In your browser’s settings, there should be an option to remove cookies. The domain that we set cookies during your use of our Apps is buysellads.com.

### 7\. If I Have Questions Concerning This Privacy Policy?

If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please contact us by e-mail at support@buysellads.com or by U.S. mail to P.O. Box 55071 #30027, Boston, MA 02205-5071.

– End –
